

My love for new challenges has brought me to this exciting journey of web development. After over 5 years of working in IT projects in various roles and fully trained as a React Developer, I'm ready to contribute to facing your specific challenges.

0

FR: +33 6 52 80 00 25 PL: +48 727 780 075



zurek.katarzyna@gmail.com



Katarzyna Zurek



github.com/Kasia307584



www.portfolio.com

Expertise



















HTML - CSS - JavaScript -React.js - Redux - Sass -Bootstrap - Git - GitHub - npm

Languages

French - English - Polish

Interests

Women in Tech and some other associative projects,

Yoga and meditation practice

Katarzyna Żurek

React Developer



Apartment rental | React | Router

www.kasa.com

- Routing with product ID, error page
- JSON data use
- Responsive application

Banking app | React | Redux

www.argent-bank.com

- API authentificaiton
- Back-end with MongoDB installation
- API design
- State management with Redux

Sports analytics | React | Recharts

www.sport-see.com

- Advanced graphics using JavaScript library Recharts
- Ensure the quality of an application's data
- Interact with a web service

HR app | React | Bootstrap

www.wealth-health.com

- Switch from jQuery to React to reduce tech debt
- NPM package release
- Performance tests (Lighthouse)
- Full code documentation

Experience

Web Content Manager

2019 - 2021

Emma Lavelle Co. | Madrid | Remote

Managed English learning platform built from Squarespace CMS website builder.

Consultant in IT projects

2014 - 2018

IT-NewVision (clients: Suez, Enedis) I Paris

Different roles in large-scale IT projects of French companies operating in the utility sector: Suez's implementation of CRM and billing software Oracle Utilities CCB for 12 million users and Enedis's construction of an HMI solution in interface with a Big Data database. Also, lead role in ERP Saas implementation at IT-NewVision.

Business Analyse - Analysed, set and fixed billing data for migration to the Oracle CCB system

PMO - Provided bug-tracking and performance indicators to engineering and management

PANTical and Business Controller - Controlled and improved invoicing process

Organisational Consultant

Crédit Agricole Technologies I Paris

2013

Education

Javascript React Developer

2021 - 2023

Bachelor, RNCP bac+3/4 (OpenClassrooms, France)

Professional diploma referenced by the French state and issued by the largest European online school. The program fully project-oriented with 14 professional projects and support from an experienced mentor.

Organizational Consulting and Change Management

Master (University of Paris 8, #47 of 224 in France)

Literature and Sociology

2011

2013

Master (University of Wrocław, Poland)